上一道小测验的方案说
The solution of the previous quiz said that we
我们需要在两处定义具体宽度的fragment布局
had to define the wide detail fragment layout in two
layout-land目录和layou-sw600dp目录。为了防止
places. The layout-land and the layout-sw600dp folder. To avoid having
有这个文件的多份附件，我们应当使用布局别名。
multiple copies of this file, we should use layout aliasing.
我们可以查看布局别名的文档来看看示例。
We can check the documentation for layout aliases to see
比方说我们有一个主布局文件给
an example. Say we have a main layout file that's
单面板的UI。在layout-large和layout-sw600dp目录中，
for one pane UI. In the layout large and layout-sw600dp
我们想要有一个多面板的布局。
folders, we want a multi pane layout. In case you're
你要是想了解，layout-large是为了对安卓3.2
wondering, layout large is for backward compatibility purposes for
之前的大尺寸设备做向后兼容的，那之后
large devices prior to Android 3.2, that's when the SW
SW限定语才被引入。所以回到刚才。
qualifiers were introduced. So back to the point. To
为了避免代码重复，我们可以在基础布局目录中
avoid code duplication, we can define the two pane layout
定义双面板的的布局。然后，在values-large
in the base layout folder. Then, in the values-large
和values-sw600dp目录中，我们再创建一份引用
and values-sw600dp folders, we can create a reference so that
这样主布局实际就映射到双面板布局了。
the main layout actually maps to the two pane layout.
在Java代码中，你可以使用R.layout.main来引用他，
In the Java code, you can reference it as r.layout.main,
但他实际上会引用到双面板布局。
but it's actually referencing the two pane layout.
这就是detail fragment最终看起来的样子。
This is what the detail fragment should look
这是手机
like afterwards. And this is what the phone
水平视图看起来的样子。如果你旋转设备，
landscape view looks like. If you rotate the
手机垂直视图将会是不一样的。
device, the phone portrait view should be different.
在下一个编码任务中，我们将要使
In the next coding task, we're going to make
今日列表项在平板上看起来更像其他项。
the today list item look more like the other items in the list for the tablet.